[
  {
    "type": "instructions",
    "note": "Each question is followed by four options lettered A to D. Find the correct option for each question"
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "1",
    "question": "Express 0.000047, correct to 2 significant figures.",
    "answer": "B",
    "options": {
      "A": "0.0",
      "B": "0.00004",
      "C": "0.000041",
      "D": "0.0000407"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "7",
    "question": "Given that a = log7 and b = log2, express log35 in terms of a and b",
    "answer": "C",
    "options": {
      "A": "a + b + 1",
      "B": "ab - 1",
      "C": "a - b + 1",
      "D": "b - a + 1"
    }
  },{
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "10",
    "question": "A sum of N18,100.00 was shared among 5 boys and 4 girls with each boy taking N20.00 more than each girl. Find a boy's share.",
    "answer": "A",
    "options": {
      "A": "x = N1,820.00",
      "B": "x = N2,000.00",
      "C": "x = N2,020.00",
      "D": "x = N2,040.00"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "11",
    "question": "One factor of 7x2 + 33x - 10 is",
    "answer": "A",
    "options": {
      "A": "7x + 5",
      "B": "x - 2",
      "C": "7x - 2",
      "D": "x - 5"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "13",
    "question": "Simplify: 3x - (p -x) - (r -p)",
    "answer": "B",
    "options": {
      "A": "2x - r",
      "B": "2x + r",
      "C": "4x - r",
      "D": "2x - 2p - r"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "16",
    "question": "The dimensions of a water tank are 13cm, 10cm and 70cm. If it is half filled with water, calculate the volume of water in litres.",
    "answer": "A",
    "options": {
      "A": "4.5 litres",
      "B": "7.50 litres",
      "C": "8.10 litres",
      "D": "9.55 litres"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "17",
    "question": "If the totals surface area of a surface hemisphere is equal to its volume, find the radius.",
    "answer": "B",
    "options": {
      "A": "3.0cm.",
      "B": "4.5cm.",
      "C": "5.0cm.",
      "D": "9.0cm."
    }
  },{
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "18",
    "question": "Which of the following is true about parallelograms?",
    "answer": "C",
    "options": {
      "A": "Opposite angles are supplimentary.",
      "B": "Opposite angles are complimentary.",
      "C": "Opposite angles are equal.",
      "D": "Opposite angles are reflex angles."
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "24",
    "question": "If P(2, 3) and Q(2, 5) are points on a graph, calculate the length PQ.",
    "answer": "D",
    "options": {
      "A": "6 units",
      "B": "5 units",
      "C": "4 units",
      "D": "2 units"
    }
  },
  {
    "type": "quiz",
    "no": "33",
    "question": "In what number base was the addition 1 + nn = 100, where n > 0, done?",
    "answer": "B",
    "options": {
      "A": "n - 1",
      "B": "n",
      "C": "n + 1",
      "D": "n + 2"
    }

  }
]
